Amanda Seale Show today goes to the sun for making it the perfect day to protest against
genocide. Yesterday was a global day of protest against the genocide in Gaza and that's exactly
what people did. So in Chicago, protesters straight up blocked traffic heading into O'Hare
National Airport to stand in solidarity with Palestine. You know what? You know that your
war is on some BS when Chicago has to tell you to stop the violence. Like that says a lot.
Similar protests are taking place in Oakland, California and San Antonio, Texas. Even the
Golden Gate Bridge took a break from its usual duties when protesters shut it down in both
directions. So shout out to all the white people who thought they were taking a nice scenic drive
across the Golden Gate Bridge and found themselves stuck in Oakland. What's my favorite word?
The letdown goes to the apparent fabric shortage at Nike factories.
Wow. Nike dropped its... Yeah, because they dropped their Olympics women's track and field
outfits and the ladies are not feeling it. They're calling it to revealing and sexist.
Must be due to a fabric shortage because baby, I don't understand how they're going to run in this.
One athlete was quoted as saying, my hoo-ha is going to be out. Nike, here's a thought. How about
consulting the women athletes about what they need? And next time your male executives decide to approve
designs for women athletes. Just don't do it.